大家好我是Everyday Astronaut频道的Dodd
Hi it's me Tim Dodd the Everyday Astronaut
咱们频道一直致力于
My mission has always been
让老百姓了解航天了解太空
to bring space down to Earth for everyday people
我意识到不是每个人都有机会
And I realize that not everyone will get a chance
近距离亲自看看火箭
to get up close and personal with rockets in their lifetime
而即使你真的去肯尼迪航天中心看火箭，周围各种东西都那么大
And even when you do see the rockets at say, the Kennedy Space Center, everything is just so big
你还是很难感觉尺寸到底如何
it's hard to have a good sense of scale
所以为了让你了解火箭到底有多大
So in order to help you understand just how big rockets are
我决定把它们带回地球
I decided to bring them down to earth
我想到了一个很好的办法来展现它们的体型
I figure the best way to help show off their size
就是把它们放进日常生活中
is to put them in everyday settings
放进各种大家熟悉的地标建筑中
amongst landmarks you might be familiar with
猎鹰九号火箭的图片你们肯定都见过
I mean, after all, I'm sure we've all seen pictures of a Falcon 9
但只有看到像这样的照片你才能意识到火箭到底有多大
but it isn't until you see a picture like this that makes you appreciate just how massive these things are
废话少说，一起来看看吧！
Without further ado, may I present rockets in everyday places
接下来听我扯两句
So ready for a crazy story?
这视频是我和我朋友Oli Braun一起做的
I had been working on this video with my friend Oli Braun
就是去年秋天开始造各种火箭模型那老哥
you know, the guy who makes these amazing model rockets, since last fall
我们甚至一年前就开始拍素材，写曲子
We even shot some of the aerial footage and I wrote that song a year ago
做的过程中我们看Reddit上看到了类似的内容
As we were working on it, we saw someone on Reddit post a similar concept
然后我就去找了他，名叫Mattew Nayman
So I reached out to him, his name's Matthew Nayman
发现他的那个视频已经快完成了
Come to find out he was already about done with an almost identical video
然后我们就一起合作完成了你们刚刚看到的视频
so we teamed up to finish the video you just watched
当我们马上就要剪完片子的时候
So as we're making the final edits in this video
该视频在av25246469 视频说明里也有
我又看到了Corridor Crew的视频
I see the Corridor Crew posted an almost identical concept of this video as well
你说巧不巧
And theirs is absolutely amazing
简直太巧了
This is getting too weird
好吧我只能说英雄所见略同
Well I guess great minds think alike
而这也正是航天的魅力所在
and that just goes to show just how inspiring and influential spaceflight truly is
这也正是我想做的——
So to me, that's what this is all about
让每个人更加了解航天
Getting everyone excited about spaceflight
让大人们找回孩童时仰望星空的自己
Helping adults reminisce about their childhood awe of the cosmos
激发下一代对太空探索的好奇心与求知欲
Sparking curiosity in future generations to dream about exploration, thirst for knowledge
让他们找到自己在茫茫宇宙中的位置
and desire to find their place in the universe
所以记得去看看Matthew和Corridor Crew的视频
So be sure and check out Matthew's video for some bonus footage, definitely check out the Corridor Crew's amazing video
如果你想要细节最完美的火箭模型
and if you're interested in the most detailed model rockets
记得去这个网站哦
ever, be sure and check out BuzzSpaceModels.com
另外特别感谢Rotor Visuals的Ben Stineman
I also owe a special thanks to Ben Stineman of Rotor Visuals
帮助我们制作这个视频
for helping with some of the aerial shots
当然，和我往期视频一样
and of course, like all my videos and content
没有你们的Patreon赞助(投币与充电)就没有我的今天
I couldn't do this without the help of my Patreon supporters
他们在文案、调查、Discord和Reddit子板块等方面帮助很多
They help me script, research, and do lots of other fun stuff on our exclusive Discord and our exclusive subreddit
想赞助欢迎去下面这个链接
If you wanna help contribute please visit Patreon.com/everydayastronaut
非常感谢
Thank you
和往常一样，我所有视频的音乐都是原创的
As always, all the music in my videos is original
包括这个视频
Including this song for this video
音乐名叫The Scale Of It All
called The Scale Of It All
在下面这个链接可以免费下载
Check it out for free at Soundcloud.com/everydayastronaut
感谢各位，我要说的就这些
Thanks everybody, that does it for me
我是Tim Dodd，来自Everyday Astronaut频道，字幕翻译给虫
I'm Tim Dodd, The Everyday Astronaut
让航天走进寻常百姓家
bringing space down to Earth for everyday people, and rockets, too